A Guide to the Mutual Assurance Society of Virginia General Business Records, 1795-1965
Library of Virginia
- Series IV: General Accounts, 1799-1913 (bulk 1799-1865) 12.15 cubic feet (27 boxes); Boxes 81-107
  - Claims, 1796-1798 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    1798 Means, Robert (Richmond)
    1798 Murray, George (Fredericksburg)
    1798 Peyton, Craven (Albemarle Co.)
    1798 Winston, George (Richmond)
  - Claims, 1799 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    1799 Baldry, William (Norfolk)
    1799 Burke, Margaret (Norfolk)
    1799 Christie, James (Norfolk)
    1799 Dick, William (Norfolk)
    1799 Gardner, James (Norfolk)
    1799 Graham, Tildsley (Norfolk)
    1799 Heary, Matthew (Norfolk)
    1799 Herndon, William (Fredericksburg)
    1799 Higgins, Samuel (Norfolk)
    1799 Mitchell, George (Norfolk)
    1799 Mitchell, John (Norfolk)
    1799 Redman, Herman (Norfolk)
    1799 Warren, John (Norfolk)
    1799 Woodside, John (Norfolk)
  - Claims, 1803-1809 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    1803 Duval, William (Richmond)
    1803 Muncaster, John
    1804 Ashley, Warren (Norfolk)
    1804 Burton, May (Orange Co.)
    1804 Casey, Demsey (Norfolk)
    1804 Christie, James (Norfolk)
    1804 Deans, James and Robert Chapman (Alexandria)
    1804 Hartshorn, William (Alexandria)
    1804 Kean, Ann (Winchester)
    1804 Mills, Charles (Louisa Co.)
    1804 Pollard, Robert (King and Queen Co.)
    1804 Ruffin, George (Prince George Co.)
    1804 Smith, Armistead (Mathews Co.)
    1804 Vashan, Simon (Norfolk)
    1805 Bedinger, Daniel (Berkeley Co.)
    1807 Lester, Sarah (Richmond)
    1807 Lyon, Peter
    1808 Ross, James (Fredericksburg)
    1809 Anderson, Robert (Alexandria)
  - Claims, 1815 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    1815 Adams, Ashley (Dinwiddie Co.)
    1815 Archer, John (Amelia Co.)
    1815 Bullock, David (Richmond)
    1815 Crouch, Richard (Richmond)
    1815 Crutchfield, Stapleton (Spotsylvania Co.)
    1815 Darracott, John (Hanover Co.)
    1815 Dunlop, John (Petersburg)
    1815 Durkin, Patrick (Petersburg)
    1815 Gilmour, William (Petersburg)
    1815 Hoomes, John (Caroline Co.)
    1815 Horner, Gustavus B. (Fauquier Co.), includes will
    1815 Ingram, John (Norfolk)
  - Claims, 1815 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    1815 Johnston, Richard (Fredericksburg)
    1815 Johnston, Robert (Richmond)
    1815 Judah, Manuel (Richmond)
    1815 Laforest, Joseph A. (Richmond)
    1815 Moore, Archibald (Petersburg)
    1815 Taliaferro, Francis M. (Spotsylvania Co.)
    1815 Turner, Daniel (Caroline Co.)
    1815 Turner, Samuel (Petersburg)
    1815 Wilcox, Richard
  - Claims, 1816 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    1816 Bolling, Robert (Petersburg)
    1816 Bradley, Elizabeth (Cumberland Co.), includes will of William Bradley
    1816 Henderson, Johnston (Petersburg)
    1816 Heath, James (Fredericksburg)
    1816 Knox, James (Petersburg)
    1816 McKim, Alexander (Richmond)
    1816 McKim, Robert (Richmond)
    1816 Randolph, Ann (Henrico Co.)
    1816 Washington, Sarah (Westmoreland Co.), includes will of William A. Washington
  - Claims, 1817 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    1817 Corbin, Richard (Caroline Co.)
    1817 Hannon, Richard (Petersburg)
    1817 Loyall, George and Robert C. Jennings (Norfolk)
    1817 Smith, Mary (Fredericksburg)
    1817 Swann, John (Powhatan Co.), includes will of John Swann
    1817 Thomas, Benajah (Richmond)
    1817 Watkins, William M. (Charlotte Co.)
    1817 Willis, Lewis (Fredericksburg), includes will of Lewis Willis
  - Claims, 1818 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    1818 Blair, John D. (Richmond)
    1818 Cooke, John (Stafford Co.)
    1818 Enders, John (Richmond)
    1818 Foster, Aeneas (Richmond)
    1818 Grimes, William H. and Lilly Knight Grimes (Norfolk), includes will of William G. Knight
    1818 Harris, Lucy A. (Richmond)
    1818 Isbell, Thomas H. (Cumberland Co.)
    1818 Meade, Richard (Amelia Co.)
    1818 Mitchell, James (Fredericksburg)
    1818 Roane, Spencer (Hanover Co.)
    1818 Robinson, Robert (Richmond)
    1818 Scherer, Sarah (Richmond)
    1818 Smith, Mary (Fredericksburg)
    1818 Stith, John (Petersburg)
    1818 Warren, John (Norfolk)
    1818 Willis, Byrd C. (Spotsylvania Co.)
    1818 Woode, Amelia Harris (Richmond)
  - Claims, 1823-1825 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    1823 Quarles, William (Fredericksburg)
    1824 Enders, John (Richmond)
    1824 Peacock, Richard (Fredericksburg)
    1824 Wilcox, Thomas (Petersburg)
    1824 Wright, Thomas (Fredericksburg)
    1825 Ballay, Francis (Norfolk)
    1825 Newton, George (Norfolk)
    1825 Henley, Robert (Norfolk)
    1825 Pollard, Henry (Richmond)
    1825 Todd, Mallory (Norfolk)
  - Claims, 1835-1861 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    1835 Allison, Wilham and William Smith (Richmond)
    1835 Bowen, William (Stafford Co.)
    1835 Crane, James C. (Richmond)
    1835 Eustace, John H. (Richmond)
    1835 Green, Duff (Stafford Co.)
    1835 Payne, William (Stafford Co.)
    1835 Pleasants, Deborah (Richmond)
    1835 Reins, Richard (Richmond)
    1835 Smith, William (Richmond)
    1861 Barclay, Selina (Norfolk)
  - Claims, unknown (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Claims, Statements of county losses, 1808 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Claims, Statements of town losses, 1797-1828 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Claims, Oversize, 1797-1815 (Box 86)
    1797 McMara, Patrick (Richmond)
    1799 French, George (Fredericksburg)
    1799 Parsons, William (Fredericksburg)
    1799 Patton, Robert (Fredericksburg)
    1799 Walker, Robert (Fredericksburg)
    1799 Unknown (Fredericksburg)
    1799 Unknown (Norfolk)
    1806 Smock, James (Fredericksburg)
    1808 Minor, Garett
    1815 Bell, John (Petersburg)
    1815 Bolling, Robert (Petersburg)
    1815 Bolling, Robert and Frances Boyle (Petersburg)
    1815 Bosher, Charles (Richmond)
    1815 Bowden, William (Petersburg)
    1815 Byrne, James (Petersburg)
    1815 Colquhoun, Thomas (Petersburg)
    1815 Cumming, John (Petersburg)
    1815 Cummings, William (Petersburg)
    1815 Curtis, Benjamin (Petersburg)
    1815 Davis, Samuel (Petersburg)
    1815 Geddy, Elizabeth K. (Petersburg)
    1815 Jones, Churchill M. (Richmond)
    1815 Knox, James (Petersburg)
    1815 Lockhead, James (Petersburg)
    1815 McCulloch, Peter M. (Petersburg)
    1815 Nuttall, John (Petersburg)
    1815 Prentis, William (Petersburg)
    1815 Robertson, David (Petersburg)
    1815 Robertson, William (Petersburg)
    1815 Strachan, Alexander G. (Petersburg)
    1815 Twitt, William and Jones Mitchell (Petersburg)
    1815 Wilder, John (Petersburg)
  - Claims, Oversize, 1816-1835 (Box 87)
    1816 Carmichael, James (Fredericksburg)
    1816 Colquhoun, William (Petersburg)
    1816 Edmundson, David (Rockbridge Co.)
    1816 Harris, Nathaniel (Petersburg)
    1816 James, William (Fredericksburg)
    1816 Neilson, William (Chesterfield Co.)
    1816 Pendleton, William and French Strother (Culpeper Co.)
    1816 Redd, John (Cumberland Co.)
    1816 Singleton, Richard (Gloucester Co.)
    1816 Strode, John (Culpeper Co.)
    1816 Taliaferro, Hay (Orange Co.)
    1816 White, Henry (Fredericksburg)
    1817 Field, John (Gloucester Co.)
    1817 Gracie, Archibald (Petersburg)
    1817 Lemon, George (Berkeley Co.)
    1817 Lightfoot, Philip (Caroline Co.)
    1817 Rush, William (Berkeley Co.)
    1818 Balson, William (Norfolk)
    1818 Dove, John and John Enders (Richmond)
    1818 Singleton, Richard (Gloucester Co.)
    1824 Lloyd, John (Petersburg)IN BOX 86 DUE TO SIZE
    1825 Bank of Virginia (Portsmouth)
    1825 Dunlop, James (Chesterfield Co.)
    1825 Dunscomb, Daniel L. (Richmond)
    1825 Hall, LaRoy (Chesterfield Co.)
    1825 Lewis, Richmond (Richmond)
    1825 Littlepage, Letitia (Richmond)
    1825 Taylor, Robert (Norfolk)
    1825 Tichenon, Nehemiah (Richmond)
    1835 Francis, William (Norfolk)
  - Daily reports of risks of annual policies, 1885-1887 (No. 1521-1957) (Box 88)
  - Daily reports of risks of annual policies, 1887-1889 (No. 1958-2188) (Box 88)
  - Deeds, Bedford Co., 1793 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    1793 John Talbot to Callohill Mennis
  - Deeds, Culpeper Co. 1800-1802 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    1800 Nathaniel Pinkard and Daniel Stringer to John Mercer
    1802 Mordicai Barbour to John Brown
  - Deeds, Fredericksburg, 1793-1807 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    1751 Richard Royston to William McWilliams
    1792 Henry Lee Gaskins to Ann Selden (OVERSIZE ON SHELF)
    1793 George Weedon to Collen Milne (OVERSIZE ON SHELF)
    1799 James Somerville to John Chew
    1801 Alexander L. Roe to Robert Chew
    1803 Alexander L. Roe to Henry Thompson
    1805 Thomas L. Lomax and John Minor to Richard Johnson and James Young
    1805 Walter Gregory to William James
    1807 Richard Johnson and James Young to Leslie Stewart
  - Deeds, Goochland Co., 1811 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    1811 Thomas Norvell to Anthony Smith (includes will of Thomas Norvell)
  - Deeds, Henrico County, 1782-1783 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    1782 Charles Lewis to James Roane
    1783 James Roane to William Pennock (OVERSIZE ON SHELF)
  - Deeds, Loudoun Co., 1804 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    1804 Mahlon Hough to Jonah Hough
  - Deeds, Lynchburg, 1826 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    1826 Christopher Anthony to Mutual Assurance Society
  - Deeds, Norfolk, 1765-1803 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    1765 John Smith to John Woodside
    1791 John E. Holt to John Mitchell
    1793 William Eyre to Maclure and Moore
    1794 Robert Taylor and Moses Myers to John Taylor and Edward Roberts
    1795 John Trimble to William Willoughby
    1799 James Brew to Moses Russell
    1799 John E. Holt to James Brew
    1799 John Taylor to Alexander McClure
    1799 John Mitchell to John G. Brown
    1801 Robert Woodside to John Dudgeon
    1801 Mary and John Marsden to John G. Brown
    1803 Robert Chapman and John McPhail to James Deanes
    1803 John G. Brown to William Deacon and Elizabeth Smith
  - Deeds, Petersburg, 1802-1820 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    1802 James Geddy to John Taliaferro
    1807 Benjamin W. Leigh to John Wilder
    1820 Peter McLean and John Lloyd to John Patterson and Robert McLean
  - Deeds, Prince Edward Co., 1806 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    1806 John C. Miller to Thomas Eldridge
  - Deeds, Richmond, 1801-1804 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    1801 Francis Alison to John D. Blair
    1803 John D. Blair to Samuel McCraw
    1804 Nancy Campbell to Samuel McCraw
  - Deeds, Stafford County, 1808 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    1808 Robert Dunbar to William Richards (includes will of Samuel Selden, 1790)
  - Deeds, Georgetown, D.C., 1820 (Box 89, Folder 12a)
    1820 John Crewe to Clement Smith
  - Deeds, Unknown, 1802-1804 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Journal, 1852-1853 (Box 89)
  - Judgments, 1796-1835 (Box 89, Folder 13a)
  - List of sundry debts, 1814-1820 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Notices to withdraw insurance, 1800-1805 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Notices to withdraw insurance, 1806 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Notices to withdraw insurance, 1809-1816 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Notices to withdraw insurance, 1818 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Notices to withdraw insurance, 1819 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Notices to withdraw insurance, 1820 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Notices to withdraw insurance, 1821 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Notices to withdraw insurance, 1822-1834 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Notices to withdraw insurance, 1835-1848 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Notices to withdraw insurance, 1858-1865 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Power of attorney, 1837 (Box 91, Folder 3a)
  - Transfers of property and policies, 1796-1805 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Transfers of property and policies, 1806-1812, 1816 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Transfers of property and policies, 1821-1859 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1798-1801 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1802 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1803 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1805 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1806-1807 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1808 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #1-60, 1809 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #61-110, 1809 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #111-133, 1809 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1810-1815 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #1-70, 1816 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #71-165, 1816 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1816 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1817 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #1-58, 1818 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #60-120, 1818 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1818 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #1-50, 1819 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #51-127, 1819 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1819 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1820 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1821 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1822 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1823 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1824 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1825 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1826 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1827 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #10-50, 1828 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #51-80, 1828 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #83-100, 1828 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #101-149, 18285 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #150,205, 1828 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1830-1836 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #1-30, 1837 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #31-60, 1837 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #61-135, 1837 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1837 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #136-190, 1838 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #191-250, 1838 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1838 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #251-300, 1839 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #301-364, 1839 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1839 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #365-400, 1840 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #401-430, 1840 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #431-473, 1840 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1840 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #474-525, 1841 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #526-545, 1841 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #545-593, 1841 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1841 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #594-640, 1842 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #641-685, 1842 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #686-740, 1842 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1842 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1843 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1843 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1843 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1843 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1844 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1844 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1844 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1845 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1845 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1846 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1846 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1847 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1847 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1848 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1848 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1848 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1849 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1849 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1849 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1850 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1850 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1851 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1851 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1851 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1852 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1852 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1853 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1853 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1853 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1854 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1854 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1854 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1855 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1855 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1855 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1856 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1856 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1856 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1857 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1857 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1857 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1858 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1858 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1858 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1859 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1859 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1859 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1860 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1860 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1861 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1862 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and receipts, #677-694, 1864 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1865 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers and receipts, 1876-1899 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers and receipts, Nd (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers and Receipts, Alexander H. Rutherfoord, Receipts and contracts for homes in Richmond, 1842-1853 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers and Receipts, J.B. Danforth, Office and personal expenses, 1847-1865 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers and Receipts, Office expenses ledger, 1837-1872 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers and Receipts, John Rutherfoord, Agreements and receipts for office expenses, 1837-1844 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers and Receipts, Uncollected policy payments, 1819-1851 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers and Receipts, Oversize, 1822-1827
  - Will of John Baggott, Spotsylvania Co., 1773 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Will of William Booker, Amelia Co., 1795 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Will of William Osborn, Loudoun Co., 1805 (Box 107, Folder 7a)
  - Will of Thomas Paxton, Rockbridge Co., 1788 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Will of George Weedon, Fredericksburg, 1793 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1816-1837 (Box 107, Folder 10)
- Series V: Inspection reports, 1944-1965 2.1 cubic feet; 21 volumes on shelf
  Arranged numerically by volume number. Missing Volume 1.
  - Volume 2, No. 45001-45400, 1944-1945 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 3, No. 45401-45800, 1945-1946 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 4, No. 45801-46200, 1946 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 5, No. 46201-46600, 1946-1947 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 6, No. 46601-47100, 1947 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 7, No. 47101-47600, 1947-1948 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 8, No. 47601-48200, 1948-1949 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 9, No. 48201-48700, 1949 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 10, No. 48701-49300, 1950 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 11, No. 49301-49800, 1950-1951 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 12, No. 49801-50400, 1951-1952 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 13, No. 50401-51000, 1952 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 14, No. 51001-51700, 1952-1953 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 15, No. 51701-52300, 1954-1955 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 16, No. 52301-52900, 1955-1957 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 17, No. 52901-53500, 1957 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 18, No. 53501-54100, 1957-1958 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 19, No. 54101-55100, 1958-1959 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 20, No. 55101-56100, 1959-1961 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 21, No. 56101-56900, 1961-1963 (Volume On shelf)
  - Volume 22, No. 56901-57900, 1963-1965 (Volume On shelf)
- Series VI: Collection lists and Town and Country Quotas, 1796-1884 23 cubic feet (46 boxes); Boxes 108-141
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Collection lists, 1847 (Box 108)
  - Collection lists, 1848 (Box 108)
  - Collection lists, 1849 (Box 109)
  - Collection lists, 1850 (Box 109)
  - Collection lists, 1851 (Box 109)
  - Collection lists, 1852 (Box 110)
  - Collection lists, 1853 (Box 110)
  - Collection lists, 1854 (Box 110)
  - Collection lists, 1855 (Box 111)
  - Collection lists, 1856 (Box 111)
  - Collection lists, 1857 (Box 111)
  - Collection lists, 1858 (Box 112)
  - Collection lists, 1859 (Box 112)
  - Collection lists, 1860 (Box 112)
  - Collection lists, 1861 (Box 113)
  - Collection lists, 1862 (Box 113)
  - Collection lists, 1863 (Box 113)
  - Collection lists, 1866 (Box 114)
  - Collection lists, 1867 (Box 114)
  - Collection lists, 1868-1871 (Box 115)
  - Collection lists, 1879 (Box 116)
  - Collection lists, 1880 (Box 116)
  - Collection lists, 1881 (Box 117)
  - Collection lists, 1882 (Box 117)
  - Collection lists, 1883 (Box 118)
  - Collection lists, 1884 (Box 118)
  - Country quotas, 1820 (Box 119)
  - Country quotas, 1822 (Box 119)
  - Miscellaneous town and country reports, 1810 (Box 119A)
  - Statements showing value of houses in Fredericksburg, 1796 and 1822 (Box 119A)
  - Town and Country quotas, 1796-1812 (Box 120)
  - Town quotas, 1819 (Box 121)
  - Town quotas, 1820 (Box 121)
  - Town quotas, 1821 (Box 121)
  - Town quotas, 1822 (Box 122)
  - Town quotas, 1823 (Box 122)
  - Town quotas, 1824 (Box 122)
  - Town quotas, 1825 (Box 123)
  - Town quotas, 1826 (Box 123)
  - Town quotas, 1827 (Box 123)
  - Town quotas, 1828 (Box 124)
  - Town quotas, 1829 (Box 124)
  - Town quotas, 1830 (Box 124)
  - Town quotas, 1831 (Box 125)
  - Town quotas, 1832 (Box 125)
  - Town quotas, 1833 (Box 126)
  - Town quotas, 1834 (Box 126)
  - Town quotas, 1835 (Box 127)
  - Town quotas, 1836 (Box 127)
  - Town quotas, 1837 (Box 128)
  - Town quotas, 1838 (Box 128)
  - Town quotas, 1839 (Box 128)
  - Town quotas, 1840 (Box 129)
  - Town quotas, 1841 (Box 129)
  - Town quotas, 1842 (Box 129)
  - Town quotas, 1843 (Box 130)
  - Town quotas, 1844 (Box 130)
  - Town quotas, 1845 (Box 130)
  - Town quotas, 1846 (Box 131)
  - Town quotas, 1847 (Box 131)
  - Town quotas, 1848 (Box 131)
  - Town quotas, 1849 (Box 132)
  - Town quotas, 1850 (Box 132)
  - Town quotas, 1851 (Box 132)
  - Town quotas, 1852 (Box 133)
  - Town quotas, 1853 (Box 133)
  - Town quotas, 1854 (Box 133)
  - Town quotas, 1855 (Box 134)
  - Town quotas, 1856 (Box 134)
  - Town quotas, 1857 (Box 134)
  - Town quotas, 1858 (Box 135)
  - Town quotas, 1859 (Box 135)
  - Town quotas, 1860 (Box 135)
  - Town quotas, 1861 (Box 136)
  - Town quotas, 1862 (Box 136)
  - Town quotas, 1863 (Box 136)
  - Town quotas, 1864 (Box 137)
  - Town quotas, 1865 (Box 137)
  - Town quotas, 1866 (Box 138)
  - Town quotas, 1867 (Box 139)
  - Town quotas, 1868 (Box 139)
  - Town quotas, 1869 (Box 139)
  - Record for Towns, 1805-1814 (Box 140)
  - Revaluation of Towns, 1805-1814 (Box 141)